<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Patanjali SLPSK</title>
    <link>https://patanjali.github.io/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Patanjali SLPSK</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 06:12:56 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://patanjali.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Samaritan: An automated framework for detecting fault attacks in hardware</title>
      <link>https://patanjali.github.io/project/proj1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 06:12:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://patanjali.github.io/project/proj1/</guid>
      <description>Automatic detection of fault vulnerabilities is a challenging problem because of the complicated attack surface. An interesting observation is that, out of the large number of faults that can occur in the design, very few faults are actually exploitable. However, there are no automated tools that can identify these exploitable fault locations in a hardware device. Hence current countermeasures cannot target these exploitable locations and incur significant overhead. Another challenge is that the designers have to ensure that the security guarantees of these countermeasures are met at every stage of the manufacturing process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SecureSizer: An gate-sizing framework for mitigating fault attacks in hardware</title>
      <link>https://patanjali.github.io/project/proj3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 06:12:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://patanjali.github.io/project/proj3/</guid>
      <description>Fault attacks are one of the growing physical attacks exploits that target edge devices. The attacker introduces faults at specific locations in the device during encryption thereby corrupting the result of the operation. These faults are introduced by either manipulating the system clock, the power supply or by using a laser. Traditional countermeasures rely on redundant logic, parity checking which introduce area and power overheads. In this work, we explore the idea of gate-sizing as a countermeasure for fault attacks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy aware Deep Learning </title>
      <link>https://patanjali.github.io/project/proj2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://patanjali.github.io/project/proj2/</guid>
      <description>The advent of IoT has led to massive data generation due to the widespread deployment of sensors, networks, and processing devices. Deep Learning has emerged as a popular computing paradigm that is used to process these large scale data and gather useful information. Of late, companies like Amazon and Google have provided cloud-based Deep Learning solutions. These solutions are referred to as Deep Learning as a Service (DLaaS). Recent works have demonstrated that these DLaaS systems are quite vulnerable to adversarial attacks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>